What's up guys Welcome This is coach EJ
and Welcome to my YouTube channel in
this video I will explain to you the
cheapest life and health insurance
of The One by fwd so Finish the
video so you understand him also
After watching this Nono make
sure to comment if you have
questions and like and subscribe so this is the
flow of our conversation so
first we're G to talk about the one
all you need to know
about the one product by fwd number two
Of course for people who don't know
who fwd is I'll also show you the
stability ah ang kasing legit and all
of the information that you need to
understand and know more about fwd life
insurance then number three a little bit
introduction about myself so
you just know me and number four if the
step by step How to sign up then last
just key products also no that
you can start with fwd So I'll
start with the one with fwd so in this
video you probably saw it on tiktok or
on my Facebook post or Wherever
nonno ah so you're here and
because you watch it it means  you're
interested in getting your life and health
insurance but it's expensive or we can't
afford it Nono so perfect
our one product So basically The
one is a renewable plan that you can
buy online So you can buy it
online I put the link where you can buy it below in the
comment section and description it can
also be bought on fwd's website but
of course because you're watching here I'm the
one educating you Use
my link so I will be your financial advisor
the good thing is no you can also buy
products or benefits according to
your taste okay it's just that it's flexible it's
not just flexible it's still very cheap
So basically we have four
variants with the one non so on the right
side If you saw it here on the screen Ah
this is the complete one this is the one I showed
on my tiktok complete The life
insurance critical illness and then
Accidental death benefit so when it says
life insurance 300,000 ' it means
if the insured dies or you die
your beneficially will receive the money that you
drank I'll show you  What are those
coverages, this health insurance?
No. You can claim if
you are diagnosed with either of those 42
critical illnesses. So you can claim it at
any hospital because you can just claim it
as Cash and lastly, it is Accidental
death benefit, meaning if
you die through an accident, there is an additional
500,000 coverage or cash benefit that
your family will receive. So this is the
most right variant that
you saw here, that is the complete one. You can also
break it down. No. If you
just want life insurance, it is listed here
on the left. Life insurance only. Or
you just want life or critical illness.
Or you can also have life and then accident.
So it depends. But you know, I
suggest you at least get insurance.
Complete it. So these are
our coverages and renewability.
You saw them here on the slides. So we can issue
age from 18 years old to 70 years old. So that's
covered. No, that's up to 70
years old. And then the critical illness
up to 80 years old. Accidental
coverage is also up to 80. Then
our life coverage. Or  life
insurance up to age 100 the one
is an annual renewable plan meaning
you pay for it annually and then
renew to have that coverage no So it's just
like car insurance 'ba usually
car insurance is
paid annually to have that kind of
security or coverage so it's the same
with the one no the good thing about it
is that we don't have a price increase for
every 5 years if you keep
paying your policy on time
Of course as you progress as you age
your insurance gets more expensive So that's
really it 'ba because as we get older
our insurance gets more expensive
So if you're still young now that's the perfect
time no to buy insurance no so it's still
cheap then even if you renew it it's still
cheap 'ba So this guys this
one even if you compare it to other
insurance companies ah no joke you're kidding it's
really cheap no um in fact if
you're 25 years old and below it's
only 2,000 or less even those who are
almost 50s 40s are still cheap no compare  you
in traditional regular pay insurance
So if you really want to cover
yourself with insurance but
you are expensive with the usual traditional insurance
This is really the perfect choice for you
We also have an exclusion Of course,
this is suicide, unlawful acts, war, that's
normal for insurance
companies so Just look at this,
this is our coverage for
critical illnesses, no 42 major critical
illness industry standards, that
means no matter what insurance
you ask, they have the same
coverage, so we have cancer here on
the left side and then the non-cancer group
when we say cancer group, um all
kinds of cancer, no from What is it,
prostate cancer, breast cancer, just in
short all kinds of cancer, late
stage cancer, that's stage 3 or stage 4,
so if you are diagnosed with late stage
cancer, you are covered for 200,000 We also have a
non-cancer group, that means it's
different, like categories,
there are major organ
failures, there are heart and blood vessels, Ah,
including heart attacks, like that,
neuromuscular diseases like stroke and
others, no, different, like major  Burns
just screenshot it so you know
what his coverage is and
of course when you buy a policy
the coverage is listed there And
there you go now I'm showing you what looks like a
table so you don't have to ask
But you can look at the coat
you can quote yourself
how much but this is just a table to give
an idea ah on the left side you can see
your age 18 19 20 on the right side
the benefit you want So for the
purpose of illustration let's say
example 18 years old 18 years old k
complete all the benefits this color
yellow on the right um for a male That's
only 1,652 a year Very cheap
really cheap female
around 1,604 Okay so that's how the
table is used for example at 30 years old if
complete benefits like complete Your
life insurance critical illness and then
ah call it Accidental death around
male around
2,252 female 2,357 so it's still very
very cheap Nono so that's how
the table is used This is from  age 31
to 50 Look there if you are 50 years old
on the right side if
the benefit you will get is complete it is
6,990 if male per year and then
6.7 45 if female per year so it is
just there on the chart Look it is
very easy to use Look at
your screenshot too so you know
you have a reference so you don't have to ask
questions okay We also have 51 to 70
Look here so you can see let's say
example no If you just want it at the age
of 70 you just want to cover
your mother your father ah uncle aunts let's
say insurance only ah 300,000 is listed
here no at age 70 for female 9,600 for
male 12,881 if let's say life
insurance only so it is still cheap it
comes out around just around Php1,000
per month 'ba So on the right side if
you complete the benefit that
you want for people that you want to cover
at 70 years old the male  is
3,900 ah plus So basically
it's still cheap if you think about it Of course
it's renewable that's there when you buy
the insurance there's how much
you'll pay every year ' Of course
every year it increases because
people's lives become more risky because
we get older and get sick Okay this is also
from 71 to 90 years old so when you get to
80 years old to 90 years old the
coverage you can only renew is life
insurance Okay you can stay
critical illness at age 79 Okay So
basically that's it but the important thing is
the coverage is still possible it's still possible
and it's still cheap
compare this coverage to regular
regular premium insurance ' even if
you compare it to regular premium
insurance so it's still cheap Ong The
one we have So if you're on the budget
this is really a perfect ah plan for you
that you can buy online you can also
claim online Everything is online so it's
so easy So what about
its process Of course, you will buy
it online so I will provide the
link where you can buy it here in the
description or in the link in my bio
that is just there it is just there no then
your initial payment you can
pay through GCash or through credit
card or through bank transfer so it is not
only GCash is it also there are many e-wallets
that can be like maya whatever no
we are very flexible there So
you can pay annual semi-annually and then
quarterly Of course you can save money if
you do it annually Okay so it is a
little cheaper no you have a discount So if
your budget can afford it then just do it annually and
not really can do it quarterly will be
fine ' ba So um nin is it yearly As I
said earlier then when you have renewed
it yearly ah just use it
you can pay again through credit card or
can be paid Through Your GCash or
maya non just use 03 plus policy
number then you will see as bills
payment Iyung fwd life insurance all
the banks major banks and then
our major e-wallets noo ah
fw life insurance is listed as a third party
biller or  bills payment so you look for
it you can pay so just put
03 plus policy number your policy number
you will get it after you pay and
approve or force your
policy Okay then of course
just put your name like that then
after you submit fwd will send
an email SAO
indicating that your policy has been approved or
your policy has been enforced then it is digital
no no we have a deed like a hard
copy Okay so our copy is digital
fwd is fast you just need an
ID ah and then the policy number When
we claim Everything is online even
the claim is fast it is still cruel
We also have an app called
omni this app you can see on Google
Play ah or in your app store it is a very
good app because you can check
BP and then you can do a lot there no there are
so many Perks and you also saw
your insurance there no
we can monitor your investments if you
have investments with fwd Okay
this app is very good omni terms of claims
so  We have a lot of ah ah kungbaga
way no but the easiest here is
make sure your requirements are complete
Of course if it's a critical illness or
It's a death the documents needed
like example death certificate or ah
doctor's diagnosis certificate
compile everything then number two
is contact your Agent non so in
case you buy from me through my link
I'll be your financial advisor ah
contact me you can see my cellphone
number here in the omni app from
fwd or that number three is you can
contact fwd via omni he has a
chatbot there you can R get
fwd's email address it's only on the website you can see it
there you can also chat with fwd on the
website Okay then after that when
you complete the documents
we just submit all the documents to process
the claims and usually as long as
our documents are complete ah if it's okay
it will be approved then
you can just get the money through
your Papa deep in the bank or through a check So
that's just a little summary ah
In short the one is very affordable
insurance that is no life health and
Accidental death  that you can just buy it
online it's renewable annually and all
claims can also be done online so it's super easy
super fast and super affordable fwd
life insurance is my partner here
in my consulting firm or being a
financial advisor why I choose fwd
because they're actually very innovative
they seem to be doing a lot of
technology based products and
systems and super fast
approval and you know if there's no fee
their cost of insurance is really cheap
relative to other insurance companies
owner and founder of fwd is Richard
Lee if you don't know Richard,
he's the son of lik Shing who is one
of the richest in Hong Kong
Actually like he's like Henry C here with
us no fwd is actually based in
Hong Kong we are listed on the Hong Kong
Stock Exchange with their parent
company noo Pacific Century group so
fwd is actually a really big company and the amount of
assets that it handles is really big, in
fact more than 7 2.9 billion US dollars
that it handles globally and
worldwide noo and in terms of rating
no rating in terms how good is
triple A  fwd's rating in
Hong Kong and here also in the Philippines is
high. Our rating is also high. No, it
means that there are many people claiming and
your company is very stable. Okay, so Geographic
from print entered the Philippines in 2014
and has already entered China. In Shanghai,
Japan and many other countries. So this is
fwd's website. Let's play
this video. Let's just take a quick
look at the corporate video.
[Music]
fwd.
[Music] k. [
Music]
k. fwd. There are many people asking. What is the
difference between fwd's agent
and other insurance companies out
there in the Philippines? I can
summarize it into four content points.
The first is that it's easy to read.
FWD's contracts are
confusing. But with fwd, it's
so simple. So anyone can easily do it.
Number two is that
his approach to claims is straight forward. There's no
fuss, the claims are fast.
As long as you complete the required information, you can get the job done.
requirements
we can think about but they are really legit
they are really fast So that's the one
there also fwd is really innovative
um we are the ones who released the most
online products no online insurance
products no including the one ' ba that
anyone can buy no that at a
cheap price that you can buy
online So even if you don't have a financial
advisor you can just buy it yourself you can also
but of course once you buy online ah
you will be strong with me as a financial
advisor if you use my link so
that will guide you ' ba and number four
last maybe is um The beauty of
fwd's technology we are the only ones who seem to be the
first with a very high-tech app
so once you become a client of fwd
we have omni earlier I showed you that
you can see everything there about the
investments about your insurance
updates as long as everything and you can
chat That omni no That app about
your concern So even if you don't have an Agent you
can still ask questions or consult
so It's really very high-tech
maybe the last thing I want to show is
this research you can do
this Nono if you Actually go to Google ah
because one way to know if it's good  is it
really or not a life insurance
company is going to the third party na na
what no na na institution just like
the insurance Commission So if you are
in Google just type insurance
Commission and for those people doesn't
know what insurance Commission is They are
the government governing body of
all insurance companies in the whole
Philippines and if you click on the website
let's go Check and then
look for the data Then click on
the statistics then life insurance
companies you will see reports do
and important
information for you to know What is a
good life insurance company that
you can invest in no um Okay There is a lot of information
here Ah for me the most
important here is Actually what we
called paid up capital So what is the
paid up capital paid up capital
ibig sabihin ng nagtay ng life insurance
Of course all the people who take out
insurance are their concern are the payers
Ong kompanyang to in a worst case
scenario the paid up capital is the
money that the insurance company
in this case fwd to the government to Secure
all the all the clients or insurers no
all the insured in a worst case scenario
Okay, their balance sheet doesn't include
their global insurer, but that's
just the money set aside by the government to
pay the people in a worst case scenario
and we can see it in the Insurance Commission
report. How much
paid up capital was put in? Okay, and you're the ones to
judge.
What do you think? But if I
open the file, let's open it here.
There it says 2022. This is
the latest data. Oh, from top one to top top
30 yet. Okay, let's enlarge it
so you can see that FWD is top 3
in terms of what we call the paid
up capital. No, so we're top 3 there. We're
so proud of that with the paid
up capital of around 2.3 billion. So in
fact, it seems like a small difference. No,
what you're seeing right now in the
screen is the paid up capital. So top 1,
top two, top 3. So good news, FWD is top three
in terms of our paid up capital
with a paid up capital of two 2.3
billion. It means that's the money set aside.
fwd in a worst case scenario for
all our clients so here are also
the other companies that
have been in the Philippines for a long time no just
like this aia BDO ah
Axa my new life and so and so forth
including Sun Life non so
their paid up capital is also listed there so
for me good plus points to with fwd
Why Why did I chose fwd because
their paid up capital is high so I'm sure that
the company really has in a worst case scenario Okay second I'm looking at called your
new businesses ibig sabihin yung mga
so let's grow
a little bit, show it here in terms
of new business so fwd won't lag behind
even though
we've been in the market for almost 10 years, our new
business is already number six, okay,
you can earn no number six fwd life, so
everything, it's nothing like if you ask me
in my experience as a financial advisor,
there are no insurance companies that have
entered the top 10 in less than 10 years.
The growth is really fast. No,
so fwd for me is one of the best companies.
Of course, let's be small because
I'm a financial advisor there, but numbers can tell.
No results can tell that the
company is really good. So if you're still in doubt,
who is fwd? fwd is that safe? fwd. This is the
government that said that fwd is really safe
and our financial stability is good.
Hopefully, that report will
give you an idea of ​​how stable the company
is and you can trust it, but you can
also do your due diligence. You can just
google it, just do your research on fwd.
Just Google it. Go to the insurance Commission
or just study it. So when you
click  That link will
take you to the website which is
the one Okay so all you need to do the
first step is click on Ong get a coat
so you can have a coat no ah then
just tap the next
one then just get the voucher
we don't have a voucher so choose your
gender  t's say mail then
date of birth let's say in the sample we're
here that's for example
ah 1998 just click
next then just put your
email address so in this example let's
just put it here let's say Juan de la
Cruz
cruise gmail.com let's click next
you can do this via laptop on the website
or you can also on cellphone no via your
Safari or Google
Chrome so just click accept and
proceed then you will have here the
variant you choose If
you choose the complete or just one no so for
example in this case ah these are
your choices for example just click on
it no so For example you want this life
insurance only that's all you choose
Of course if what you choose it will give
you an idea no how much it is
annually So if you want the life
insurance with critical illness this is it
if you want the ah Accidental death
and then life insurance This is it But
if you want the complete this is that so
choose the complete for all that
no you are here too man you are here too man
' ba So after you choose that
just click on
next then it will show what
how much it is quarterly  semiannual
and then annual you will really save more
if you make it an annual so when
you are good there click Accept and
proceed
after that we show you no is
this the ideal yearly renewable
amount Okay so of course agag I said
no it has a guarantee of 5 years with
no increase if you pay the
insurance on time so for example this it
increases as your age ah it
increases of course as
you get older but it's good there It's still
very cheap no in fact if
you look at it even at age 50 years old
here 6,000 per year it's still cheap because
with other insurance it might be your 6,000
per month no here per year It's
so very cheap when you are okay there
just click next Then this is the
summary of what you bought just click
next Then let us know ah Let us know
you first will be asked if you are Filipino like that
so let's say yes
you are Filipino Are you a US Citizen Ah just put it
no if not Then where are you located ah in the
Philippines or overseas choose
let's just say Philippines then
ah let's say I just put it here no just
answer it so let's just put it no
then let's put it no so just answer
the questions there Then
you choose where you work so
office is it independent service provider
manual labor or special class or in the
government like that Just choose or
nonworking you don't work so let's
just say office click on that then
you put it here ah Of course
Philippines then you put
your province let's say Davao del Sur
then City let's say Davao City Then
what What is the address of the work so let's
just say an example here fwd life
bahada sa sa Sample then here it's
not an example then bahad that's
just a sample so let's put it next
then what source of your income
let's say salary Then what industry
let's say you're in a call center okay just ten
Okay then when you're okay with
this Read Ong the questionnaires
medical questions Read Ong the
questionnaire then if you're goods there
ah just select all then Yes
continue then here just complete
the details
let's finish  email Just put it in then
permanent address Where is
your permanent address let's say Metro Manila let's
say Makati then ah
building
ah
for example just put it in no pretend what
any Subdivision that is no
then
ah citizenship what citizenship you are
Of course Filipino Then what id are you going to send
so to me for example lal I will send
my let's say driver's license
for example no so number lo2 for example just
pretend the expiration
date for example let's just upload that
no so just pretend this is that
we will upload then then click next
when you are okay when you have uploaded so
valid ID is all that is needed You know
what government IDs are so any
government ID will be will be will be
Okay then replacement declaration
Ah so just answer that for example
no my answer click next then
are you buying this policy on behalf of
someone other than beneficiary So no then
next Then
this you nominate a beneficiary
no so Of course you put a beneficiary
here So so that we know who is ur so that
we know who will receive the money
no so in this case  let's say let's put
ah mother for example So what is the
description of your mother gender wife just
pretend no let's say Ah
your mother's name
ah just complete it really date of
birth let's say what year
19 75 just for example let's put birth
address just complete it As in just
complete it really there What's
there so Philippines Then number
ah province that's it just finish it
ah
so Just put the address What
barangay is it like that then cellphone
number pretend then email address let's
say email address of your beneficiary
then if there is any additional
information citizenship if
you add a beneficiary click
Ong add additional beneficiary okay
then if you are okay just click
accept and
continue then you will buy how
much you will pay let's say
annual this is your annual oh only 1,880 per
year is cheap Awesome then declaration
if you are okay there declare that i
agree Of course read that first let's
read that let's accept and continue
then you are okay
just review your details when you are okay
with  your details I am paying for this
policy click on that then confirm and
pay so your application is now in dragon pay
Of course from dragon pay It's
a third party what is it no payment gateway
system choose there How will you
pay him you can bank you can credit card
or you can do that you have many options
you can do credit card debit card
Just choose what is the debit card your credit card
So let's select no Back it back
you will put your details if
it is debit or credit visa mastercard and
the details then there is also more
that GCash there is GCash So you can
select let's say in this example
you will use GCash just click on that GCash that's
it or just usually This is the
area like this You know how to
predict GCash Put GCash
number mods pay him online when
paid email SAO to the fwd of and
enforce your policy So that's all for easy
Congratulations it's that easy You have
life health and Accidental death benefit
insurance with fwd the one so very
very cheap so share this video
with your friends anti relative so they
know  They also know that there is
this cheap insurance that
they can buy Okay so this is the last video
I'll just show you What else is there in
fwd ah aside from cheap insurance
we also have investments no in the stock
market this is in the Philippines what I'm showing
you is Actually our funds we
have the Philippine Stock market
we also have it here in the US stock market
so for example Philippine Stock market
I just click ha when we click that we can see
where is it invested okay at a
cheap price of more or less ph5 to
Php3,000 per month You can start
your retirement you can also put
insurance on it and then there is an
investment too no So it can be 10
years payment period so this is the
example of investments with fwd
nonno so when the Philippine Stock market that's that's
our investment investment no invested in SM BDO Ayala and so
on and so forth So we have many
choices not just that um Usually
the growth in the stock market
averaged 15 to 20% per year
Of course it varies it's not guaranteed
but  that's the actual or that's the
average growth there are also funds
handled by Security Bank there are also funds
handled by BPI we have many
options there are stocks with high
dividends or dividend there are also
growth Driven or Consumer
Driven funds there are also investments in
other countries This is no problem so global good
esg fund when we do our clinic
we have investments in the US market or the
Global market that are good for the long
term Actually if you ask me it's good
for your retirement that's for educational
fund educational plan of your children
and you are still insured that's the good thing there
no we are still insured so these are the
examples not that where are
our examples this is it we open here this is esg
fund no or us stock market this is
so right now if you have an investment
in the Philippine market that's good if
you want to increase it PM me ah and EJ
tomorrow just test PM me to know so I can
help you no pm me on
Instagram or on my Facebook on Instagram
just choose the one with verified
check EJ bus test Okay so this is
our example funds for ah fwd to the US
market Microsoft Tesla that You know
that and he didn't just invest in the US
No but he invested in other countries
like Japan, Canada, the Netherlands so it's
very diversified,
your investment is very broad so we have
investments with fwd here that are paid one time only
meaning only once
' minimum of 100,000 we also have
funds with fwd guys that can give
regular dividends we have a
payout fund of Nitro here more or less
at 5 to 6% per year payable on a
quarterly basis that will be given SAO and
many others many Actually products
in fwd are very cheap very nice lots of
benefits So that's all that's it Pit Thank
you very much for watching the video and
share this with your friends and
comment below if you have many
questions and don't forget to like and
subscribe